your manual Life One account allows you
to use all of your money including your
income to reduce your debt over time
this could save you thousands of dollars
in interest and help you become
debt-free years sooner to get started
you'll need to take a couple of
important steps first have your pay
automatically deposited into your
account that way each time you get paid
your entire income will reduce your debt
immediately and save you interest to
have your pay deposited simply contact
the payroll person or department at your
work
place next set up all of your regular
payments to come from your manual life1
account this simplifies your banking by
making it easy to keep track of all your
expenses in one place to set up your
automatic pre-authorized payments simply
contact the appropriate company and ask
them to change your payment
information setting up your bill
payments is just as easy all you need to
do is log into your account at manif
bank.com or give us a call we'll set
them up for you by taking these simple
steps you'll be well on your way to
simplifying your banking reducing your
interest costs and becoming debt-free
sooner